Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series VI: Announcements
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements
    - Anderson, Laurie, undated (Box 1, Folder 1a.)
    - Andrucyk, Inez, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Audart, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Books & Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cafe Brazil, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cummings Arts Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Duplex Cabaret, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dursee, Brian J., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Eighth Floor Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Fotouhi Cramer Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Galapagos Space, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Gale Gates et al., undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - HERE Arts Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Himmelstein, Shelley, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Iggy Pop, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Joseph Hellman Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - J Rainey Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 17a.)
    - The Kitchen, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Lance Fung Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Malanga, Gerard, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Mann, Frank, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Martinez Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Medicine Show, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - NYU, undated (Box 1, Folder 23a.)
    - Ochiishi, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Orensanz Art Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Pardo View, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Pierogi 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Pink Inc.'s So Grand Studio, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Prospect Park Bandshell, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Randall, Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Rene's Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Roseland Ballroom, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Siberia, undated (Box 1, Folder 32a.)
    - Spectra Digital Arts Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Streb/Ringside Studio, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Subculture Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 34a.)
    - Tompkins, Betty, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Tribes Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Tricia Collins Contemporary Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Tunick, Spencer, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Upstate Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Verge, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Winter, Patricia, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Yung, Susan, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series VIII: Original Art
  - Shalom-"Millenium of Profitcy," 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stevenson, Patrick-7 Scary Planet Press Notecards, c1996: woodcarving print, handpainted (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series IX: Ephemera
  Scope and Contents note
  Accretions 1995-1999 - Series IX box
  - Ephemera: Vinnie's Friggin' Magnet and Vinnie's Tampon Case, undated (Box 19, Folder 150)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series XI: Posters
  - Cover the World poster w/art by Rodney Greenblatt, 1985 (Folder 12 Right)
  - Poetry in Motion series (sponsored by MTA, posted on MTA trains): Hal Sirowitz's "I Finally Managed to Speak to Her", undated (Folder 11 Right)
  - Ben Katchor - The Jew of New York (Folder 19)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series XII: Catalogs
  - Akashic Books, undated (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - Allied Productions, Inc., undated (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Autonomedia, undated (Box 19, Folder 153)
  - Black Sparrow Press, undated (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - Brookline Books, undated (Box 19, Folder 155)
  - Edgewise Press, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Factsheet 5, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Four Walls Eight Windows, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Hanging Loose Press, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Kaya, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Linear Arts Books, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Masquerade Books, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Mr. Puke Press, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Roof Books, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Seven Stories Press, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Small Press Distribution, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Soft Skull Press, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Spinsters Ink, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Tangerine, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - The Temple, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Thin Air Video, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Thundersmouth Press, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Undulating Bedsheets Productions, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Verso, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series XIV: Periodicals
  - American Book Review: Vol 14, No 6, Feb-Mar 1993. Vol 17, No 4, Apr-May 1996. Vol 17, No 5, Jun-Jul 1996. Vol 17, No 6, Aug-Sep 1996. Vol 18, No 1, Oct-Nov 1996. Vol 18, No 3, Mar-Apr 1997. Vol 18, No 2, Dec-Jan 1996-7., 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Blueline: Note-repros inside of Larry Webb, Shelley Himmelstein, Bob Witz, undated (Box 1, Folder 1d.)
  - Chakra: Fall 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chronogram: July 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cover: Vol 10, no 9, Holidays 1996-7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Creative Screenwriting: Vol 5, No 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Curse: Vol 3, No 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Eclectic: Vol 1, No 6, Aug 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fiction: Vol 14, No 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Home Planet News: No 41, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ikon: Vol 1, No 1, Feb 1967; Vol 1, No 5, Mar 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Juxtapoz:Vol 5, No 1, Spring 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Long Shot:Vol 22, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11a.)
  - Lusty Mover: Premier Issue, Fall 1992-Huberman, "Stark Raving Sanity" (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Masquerade: Vol 6, No 6, Nov-Dec 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meat Epoch: No 16, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Nexus: Vol 30, Fall 1994-Sparrow, "My Life in Prison," "A Ceremony," "Grapefruit," "Toilet" (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - New Observations: Issue No 123, Fall 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15a.)
  - Option: G2 Issue, Mar-Apr 1986; No 79, Mar-Apr 1998-Sonic Youth, 1986, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Out of Bounds: #2, Summer 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Paper: April 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Paramour: Vol 2, Issue 4-Unbearables Fiction: Litzky, Maynard, Rutkowski, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Poetry Calendar: Vol 21, No 6, Feb 1997. Vol 21, No 7, Mar 1997. Vol 24, No1, Sep 1999. Vol 24, No 2, Oct 1999. Vol 24, No 2, Oct 1999. Vol 24, No 3, Nov 1999., 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Poetry Project: Feb-Mar 1997, Issue #164; Apr-May 1997, Issue #165; Oct-Nov 1999, Issue #176, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Public Illumination Magazine: No 46, Late 1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rain Taxi: Vol 1, No 3, Summer 1996; Vol 1, No 4, Fall 1996; Vol 2, No1, N.d.; Vol 4, No 2, Summer 1999; Vol 4, No 3, Fall 1999. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sandbox: No 4, Winter 96-97, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Sarasota Review of Poetry: Vol 3, 1999-Jenifer Nostrand, "The sky over Versailles," "The narrow back street," "'The Army of Angels'" (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Stained Sheets: Late Summer-Early Fall 1999, Issue 23 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Sun: Issue 149, April 1988: Issue 181, Dec 1990: Issue 190, Sep 1991: Issue 194, N.d.: Issue 251, Nov 1996: Issue 257, May 1997., 1988-1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Up Front News: Jan 15, 1997; Dec 4, 1996, 1997, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Washington Free Press: No 41, Sep-Oct 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Wetbones: No 2, Fall 1997-Rob Hardin, "Exterminating the Angels" (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Wordwrights!: No 9, Winter 1997-Mary Leary, "A Certain Blue," "Modern Religion" (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series I: Correspondence
  - Kaufman, Alan, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series III: The Unbearables
  - Subseries A: The Unbearables
    - New York Times Magazine article, 2/19/95 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Daily News Article, 3//5/95, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Poetry Videos Sale Sheet, Brooklyn Bridge 95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Poster-Poetry Project's Celebration of 3 Decades, May 1997 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - W articles, 96-97, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Rent/Rant Stuff, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Crimes of the Beats
    - Life article-1957, 1959 (oversize) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Article re: Beats online, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Poster for film "Hey, Jack Kerouac," Dec 1995 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - 1996 Poetry Flash article re: Jack Kerouac (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - American Book Jam Special Issue, 8/97, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - City Magazine International (French) article, N.d. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - VLS article re Kerouac, Oct-Nov 1999 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    - Alexander, Vikky, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Benderson, Bruce, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Charnick, A., undated (Box 34, Folder 17Cooper, Dennis (oversize))
    - Cooper, Dennis, undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Delany, Samuel, undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Indiana, Gary, undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Kuper, Peter, undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Plantenga, Bart, undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Sandlin, David, undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Sapphire, undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Sparrow, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Ulin, David, undated (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Witz, Bob, undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects
    - Between C & D, undated (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Soho scene, undated (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - General Subject Misc., undated (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series VI: Announcements
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements
    - Duplex, The, undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Hsieh, Tehching, undated (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series XIV: Periodicals
  - Appearances materials for Issue #26, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Aquarian: Issue No 825, May 22-29, 1996. Issue No 827, June 5-12, 1996. Issue No 828, June 12-19, 1996. Issue No 859, Jan 15-22, 1997., 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Artforum: Sept 1973 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Books and Publishing: February 12, 1997. April 30, 1997. August 6-12, 1997. November 12-18, 1997. February 11-17, 1998., 1997-1998 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Downtown: Issue No 370, Dec 13, 1995-Jan 17, 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Get, Vol 1, No 5, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Index: Jan-Feb 1998 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - OP: July-August 1982 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Voice Literary Supplement: No 59, Oct 1987; No 60, Nov 1987; No 62, Feb 1988, 1987, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series I: Correspondence
  - Abrams, Leonard, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Andrews, Cynthia, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Atkins, Robert, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Basinski, Michael, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Berman, Rebecca, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Ben-Magid, Tam, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Bowery, Zagreus, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Bushyeager, Peter, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Cusimano, Mick, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Dijkstra, Sandra, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fagin, Betsy, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Finberg, Bonny, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Ganshaw, John E., undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Eidus, Janice, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Errol Grimes Dance Group, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Hata, Takashi, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Holman, Bob, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Huisman, Violaine, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Jankowski, Matty, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Jushi, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Kaufman, Alan, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Lamm, Gigi, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Lev, Donald, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Lifshin, Lyn, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Lytle, Ellen, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Manister, Diana, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Martinson, Neil, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Mitchell, Reverand Dr. Timothy P., undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Moore, Thurston, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Myers, Holly, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Nufer, Doug, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Packer, Eve, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Perez, Richard, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Plantenga, Bart, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Preston, Jane, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Rabinowitz, Jacob, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Raff, Colin, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Randall, Michael, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Romo, Donna, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Rossen, Anina, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Savage, Tom, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Scutti, Susan, undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Seweryn, Natalie, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Sureff, Paul E., undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Swenson, Karen, undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Swiss, Rabbi Harold, undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Talbot, John, undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Tanselle, G. Thomas, undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Tillman, Lynne, undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Topp, Mike, undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Transe, John J., undated (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Watson, Steve, undated (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Weinstein, Gail, undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Wheatstraw, P. D., undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Wuelfing, Howard, undated (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Vitale, Alfred, undated (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Unidentified / Partial Name, undated (Box 21, Folder 59)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series II: Manuscripts
  - Feast, Jim and Ron Kolm. Catalog for Roman Show of Himmelstein and Witz., undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Feast, Jim. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Finberg, Bonny. In the City of Barking Dogs., undated (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Finberg, Bonny. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Golden, Mike. For Art's Sake: A True Life Screen Trade Lesson., undated (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Hardin, Rob. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Huberman, David. Short Stories., undated (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Kolm, Ron. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Kolm, Ron. A Trail of Beer and Poetry: The Unbearables Journey through the Dive Bars of New York City., undated (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Litzky, Tsaurah. My Gladiola-A Memoir., undated (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Litzky, Tsaurah. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Maynard, Joe. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Mesmer, Sharon. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Nostrand, Jenifer. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Nufer, Doug. In the End, There Was No End., undated (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Nufer, Doug. The River Boys., undated (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Padua, JosPoetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Penn, John. Fear of Milk., undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Pirolli, John Paul. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Rutkowski, Thaddeus. Roughhouse., undated (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Ruthowski, Thaddeus. Short Fiction., undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Savage, Tom. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Schein, Lorraine. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Scutti, Susan. Shhhhhh., undated (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Sparrow. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Topp, Mike. Chinese Chipmunk., undated (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Topp, Mike. I Used to Be Ashamed of My Striped Face., undated (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Topp, Mike. A Midwestern Romance., undated (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Topp, Mike. Poetry., undated (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Vitale, Alfred. Poetry and Short Fiction., undated (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Vitale, Alfred. Yorkville., undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Watson, Carl. Poetry., undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol. Honeymoon in the Meat Packing District., undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol. Poetry., undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Witz, Bob. Poetry., undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Unknown. Lolita on the 9:25., undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Zummer, Thomas. Portraits of Robots., undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Zummer, Thomas. Projection and Dis/embodiment: Genealogies of the Virtual., undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series III: The Unbearables
  - The Unbearables Assembling Magazine Legal Issue. Issue 11, 3/5/2000. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Unbearables Assembling Magazine, Issue II - Production files (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The Unbearables Assembling Magazine Legal Issue-Production Files, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Unbearables Assembling Magazine Conspiracy Issue, Issue 13, 2/25/2001- (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Help Yourself!-book cover, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Unbearables, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Tribes Gallery reading, 5/18/2000 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - La Perla Garden reading, 8/3/2000 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - DaVinci Gallery reading, 8/13/2000 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Back Beat Festival reading, 10/5/2000 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Ultra Violet Cafeading, 3/2/2001 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Unbearables Arts Festival-Materials, 4/2001 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Unbearables Arts Festival "911" reading, 4/1/2001 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Peoples Poetry Gathering, 4/1/2001 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Bryant Park reading, 5/7/2001 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Back Fence reading, 5/13/2001 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - La Perla Garden reading, 5/25/2001 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Unbearables Arts Festival 2001-Catalogue (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Unbearables Arts Festival 2001-Mock-up of Catalogue (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Boston Newspaper Reviews of Buddah, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Article re: site of Unbearables Arts Festival in New Jersey, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    - Anthony, William, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Basinski, Michael, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Beatty, Paul, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Blagg, Max, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Branca, Glenn, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Brown, Ken, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Bush, Catherine, undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Cabico, Regie, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Coleman, Daniel, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Corso, Gregory, undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Crawford, John, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Creeley, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Crisp, Quentin, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Cusimano, Mick, undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - D'Agostino, John, undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Delany, Samuel, undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Deyab, Larry, undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Dlugos, Tim, undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Dobkin, Jess, undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Downes, Rackstraw, undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Dr. Long, undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Eggers, David, undated (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - English, Ron, undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Estep, Maggie, undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Feast, Jim, undated (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - FLY, undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Friedman, Drew, undated (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Gilbert, Sky, undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, undated (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Giorno, John, undated (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - Goldberg, Roselee, undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Hardin, Rob, undated (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Huberman, David, undated (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Kaufman, Alan, undated (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - KAZ, undated (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - Kostabi, Mark, undated (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - Kuper, Peter, undated (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - Leary, Mary, undated (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - Lida, David, undated (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Lytle, Ellen, undated (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Mazza, Cris, undated (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Mesmer, Sharon, undated (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - Nersesian, Arthur, undated (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - Nester, Daniel, undated (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - Nicosia, Gerald, undated (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - Nostrand, Jenifer, undated (Box 22, Folder 79)
    - Nufer, Doug, undated (Box 22, Folder 80)
    - Olsen, Lance, undated (Box 22, Folder 81)
    - Plantenga, Bart, undated (Box 22, Folder 82)
    - Pritchard, A. A., undated (Box 22, Folder 83)
    - Raff, Colin, undated (Box 22, Folder 84)
    - Reed, Halcomb, undated (Box 22, Folder 85)
    - Rosenbaum, Ron, undated (Box 22, Folder 86)
    - Rutkowski, Thaddeus, undated (Box 22, Folder 87)
    - Scutti, Susan, undated (Box 22, Folder 88)
    - Sirowitz, Hal, undated (Box 22, Folder 89)
    - Sparrow, undated (Box 22, Folder 90)
    - Spiegelman, Art, undated (Box 22, Folder 91)
    - Tobocman, Seth, undated (Box 22, Folder 92)
    - Ulin, David, undated (Box 22, Folder 93)
    - Vitale, Alfred, undated (Box 22, Folder 94)
    - Watson, Carl, undated (Box 22, Folder 95)
    - Wechsler, Arnold, undated (Box 22, Folder 96)
    - Weiss, Tom, undated (Box 22, Folder 97)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 22, Folder 98)
    - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated (Box 22, Folder 99)
    - Wortsman, Peter, undated (Box 22, Folder 100)
    - XYZ, Emily, undated (Box 22, Folder 101)
    - Zummer, Tom, undated (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects
    - ABC No Rio, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Art Forum, Berlin, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Autonomedia, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Barnum and Buddah Poetry Circus, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Bloomsday reading of Ulysses, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Circus Amok, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Coliseum Books, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Downtown Collection, Fales Library, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Feminist Art, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Fire of Prometheus, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Gargoyle Magazine, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Gathering of the Tribes, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - La Mama, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Low-Tech Press, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Medicinal Purposes, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Museum of Modern Art, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Performing Garage, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Poet's House, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Public Illumination Magazine, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - PS 122, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Spoleto Festival, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - The Strand, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Ten Pell Books, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - WFMU, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series V: Photographs
  - Ides of March 2000 at The Homestead Bar, photos by Lydia Tomkiw (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Photos of Chez Rollo assembled for New Observations, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Bryant Park Event, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - McManus Party, 12/21/1999; Reading at CBGB's, 1/1/2000, 1999, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series VI: Announcements
  - Subseries A: Readings
    - 2A Bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - 5C Cultural Center, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - ABC No Rio, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Allen, Roberta, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Andrews, Cynthia, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Angel Orensanz Foundation, undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Art in General, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Back Fence Poetry Reading, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Barnard, undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Barnes & Noble, undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Bergen Street Beat, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Bluestockings, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Bogosian, Eric, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Books by Artists, undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Broadsides, undated (Box 23, Folder 44)